

# Will Delorm

#### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### SUMMARY

Strong communicator with over 10 years of experience looking to utilize a creative background of generating high-quality, intuitive products as a frontend web developer.

Personal interest in gaining different perspectives and learning best avenues to solve problems.

Eager to apply strong work ethic and team collaboration to create logistical solutions for <company\_name>.

## PERSONAL DETAILS

#### Location

Eugene, OR, USA

#### CONTACT

- willdelorm@gmail.com
- 9736344619
- willdelorm.com
- in willdelorm
- willdelorm

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## WordPress Web Designer & Developer

#### SELF-EMPLOYED

2022 - Present

Provided design-to-deployment services for small businesses
Produced digital mockups of site design using Figma
Optimized sitemap to improve navigation
Expanded website to market full breadth of services offered
Established contact form to bolster client leads and retention
Trained clients to make minor edits to copy and images on platform

## Manager of Instruction

#### THE CLIFFS CLIMBING & FITNESS

2018 - 2021

Instructed trainers on best practices to ensure and instill climbers safety in a gym serving 4000 members

Collaborated on rubric with youth program to allow underage climbers to learn advanced skills Implemented and tested rope pulley systems to improve access for climbers with disabilities Maintained and inspected climbing hardware to foresee and avoid future risks Participated in restructuring of operations during the COVID-19 pandemic Adjusted class sizes to accommodate state and federal health requirements Worked with General Manager on flow of traffic to optimize social distancing Supervised staff hourly cleaning and disinfecting schedules

## Associate Lighting Designer

FREELANCE 2012 - 2017

Managed drafting and paperwork for concurrent productions providing daily updates as needed Coordinated with multiple departments the use of venue spaces to ensure all elements fit without issue

Adapted touring production around the world to produce quality experience, from a 15th century castle to a 400-seat performance venue

Learned to program a new lighting console on the fly while supervising the rest of the production set up

# **EDUCATION**

# • BFA Theatre Design / Technology

## EMERSON COLLEGE

2008 - 2012

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript, jQuery, Chrome development tools, HTML/CSS, Git, GIMP, Bootstrap, React, Node.js, MongoDB, MySQL

# **PROJECTS**

Climbing App: Tracking app for rock climbing sessions using React, Bootstrap Keeper: Google Keep clone using React TinDog: Meet cute pups in your area, using HTML/CSS